<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LocateMe</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome_screen">WelcomeScreen</string>
    <string name="common_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="grant_permission">Grant permission</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_locateme">Welcome to LocateMe!</string>
    <string name="permission_sms">SMS permissions</string>
    <string name="permission_gps">GPS permissions</string>
    <string name="welcome_explanation">Hi! This app is designed to allow family and friends to find
        each other\'s location on demand. It does not track you constantly nor does it store or
        share any of your data with any 3rd party.
        \nYou need to explicitly allow a phone number to be able to request location data from
        LocateMe installed on your phone or you need to send it to someone.</string>
    <string name="sms_explanation">LocateMe requires SMS access permissions to enable the
        functionality of sending and receiving messages. With them - LocateMe can send SMS messages
        to your friends and family to let them know your location as well as receive messages from
        them. It\'s vital for the app to function!</string>
    <string name="gps_explanation">Location permissions are necessary for LocateMe to retrieve the
        device\'s geographic coordinates. When you grant location permissions, the app gain
        privilege to request the precise location of the device, which is essential for providing
        accurate location updates to your family and friends.</string>
    <string name="help_welcome_screen">Here is the list of contacts you wish to use LocateMe with. Once you add any via button at the bottom of the screen, you can tap on a contact which will show you all the available options. From right to left, those are: \n- Remove contact, \n- Disallow given contact from being able to check your location, \n- Request contact\'s location(Note: given contact must have you added and allow you to do so,\n- Send your location to contact(That doesn\'t require another person to even use LocateMe :)).</string>
    <string name="press_to_see_help">Stay safe!\nIf you need any further explanations on how the app works:\nPress here to see help! :)</string>
</resources>